咨情室
我去趟洗手间
I got to hit the head.
我扛不住了 Bunny
I can't take this shit, Bunny.
嘿
Hey.
会过去的
It'll pass.
他们今天不过是拿你开刀
They're just riding you now.
下周就换别人了
Next week it's somebody new.
他们抢不走你的警龄 Marvin(EOD:任职日期)
They can't take away your E.O. D, Marvin.
顶多把你降回警督
The worst they can do is bust you back to lieutenant.
我已经不愿去揣测 这些混球能干出的下限
I don't even wanna think about the worst these motherfuckers can do.
你也不会想的
You don't either.
你还是没能理清案情 Marvin
You're still not connecting the dots, Marvin.
看
Have a look.
- Hoffman和Holbrook街 长官 - 很好
- Hoffman and Holbrook, sir. - Very good.
不过那儿上周刚有人横尸街头
But you had a body dropped there last week...
昨天就成这样了
and this is what the fuck it looked like yesterday.
郑重声明 这是Bond和Preston街
Bond and Preston, for the record.
Ashland和Wolfe街
Ashland and Wolfe.
Chase和Durham街
Chase and Durham.
长官 我按你的指示部署了警力
Sir, I deployed my resources per your instructions.
加强了巡逻
We've beefed up foot patrols...
便衣小队12小时出动
we have our plainclothes squads on 12-hour shifts.
而街角还是那么热闹?
And the corners stay full?
他们四处流窜 长官
They move, sir.
每天都是
Every day.
总能找到地方卖他们的毒品
They're gonna sell their drugs somewhere.
Taylor警长 我看着你那些数字
Major Taylor, I look at your numbers,
那些案情报告 照片
I see the intel reports, the photos.
都让我觉得你狗屁不知
It all tells me that you lack a fucking clue.
容我说两句
If you'll permit me.
你的副警长今天有出席吗
Is your Deputy Major present?
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
现在开始你来指挥东区分局
You now command the Eastern District.
Taylor警长 你被免职了
Major Taylor, you are relieved.
上讲台
Take the podium.
典故出自古巴比伦国王被杀的墙上预言
还有谁没看懂这"凶兆"?
Anyone else having trouble with the writing on the wall?
散会
Dismissed.
火线重案组 第三季 第三集 士兵阵亡
The Wire S03E03 Dead Soldiers
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"上帝不会拯救你"  ---Burrell
我就说 "哥们 如果你想卖我辆新车..."
And I'm like, "Nigga, if you want to sell me a new car...
"你最好真卖给我"
"you better really sell it to me.
"否则我就坐在后面看着"
"'Cause otherwise, I'm sitting back and I'm watching."
你买新车干嘛?
What you want with a new ride for?
你在这城里不是能...
Ain't like you can't get a new car anywhere you want...
随时随地买到新车嘛
anytime, in this whole city.
- 我就说说 - 说什么
- I'm just saying. - Saying what?
- 万一 - 万一什么
- In case. - In case what?
万一我想买辆新车
In case I ever want to buy a new car.
该死 这要求不过分吧
Damn, is that too much to ask for?
美女 你疯了
Girl, you crazy.
靠 趴下 趴下
Shit, shit, get down, get down.
他们察觉了
Yeah, they feeling it now.
守得滴水不漏
They protecting the fuck out of it, too.
看到你想看的了吗?
You see what you wanted?
嗯 不过他们把二楼封锁得严严实实
Yeah, man, but they got the whole second floor boarded up.
后面有个小门廊
Got a little porch around back.
几个喽啰在那守着吸薄荷烟
Couple of the boys out there now smoking on them menthols.
那我们从后面溜进去?
So we slide up from the back?
那里也封死了
That barred up, too.
没法走前门?
No way through the front?
现在不行 但到了明早...
Not now. But come tomorrow morning...
他们会把守卫人数减少到三人 懂了吗
they gonna scale back down to a three-man skeleton crew, you feel me?
我不是很喜欢这样
Not sure I like this.
我们干嘛一定要打劫Barksdale的人?
Why we got to keep hitting up the Barksdale people?
这该死的城里不是到处有毒窝吗
Ain't like this whole motherfucking city ain't got stashes all over it.
那倒是
True that.
那为什么呢
So why?
因为
Because.
因为?
Because?
就是要抢
Indeed.
就是他开枪打的警察?
So that's a cop-shooter?
嗯 他没多少前科
Yeah, not much to him.
就是在上周把Dozerman那小子(上集中弹的西区警员)那啥了
But he did that job on the Dozerman kid last week.
不过都交代了
Gave it up in a full statement.
是在你们把他揍出屎来之前还是之后?
Before or after you knocked the shit out of him?
"所受创伤均是在巡逻警员...
"Injuries were sustained while patrol officers...
"对上述疑犯施行追捕 和逮捕的过程中造成的"
"were effecting pursuit and arrest of aforementioned suspects."
- 他是在东区被捕的 对吧 - 对
- He was caught East Side, right? - Yeah.
但押解车在西区分局临时停车检修
But the wagon made a stop at the Western District for an unscheduled tune-up.
停车场里头很暗
It's dark on that back lot.
西区同事错把他当成了沙袋
Western boys mistook him for a piñata.
你看了有啥想法?
So what do you think?
我认为这是次它妈的悲剧误审
I think this is a tragic motherfucking miscarriage of justice.
我认为该成立特别陪审团...
I think it deserves a special grand jury...
不这样的话 也该由总统认命个独立检察官
and if not, the President should appoint an independent prosecutor.
不 不 事实上
No, no, no. Actually,
我认为安南同志和联合国 也该它妈的来过问一下
I think, Kofi Bryant and the United fucking Nations should get involved.
这是谋杀 Bunk
It's a murder, Bunk.
上面要我们减少而不是增加凶案的数目
The word from upstairs is that we're supposed to be having less murders, not more.
那是在Anne Arundel郡 他们干嘛在乎?
This is Anne Arundel County. Why should they care about that?
那你干嘛关心?
Why should you?
嘿 Bunk 嘿 最近怎样
Hey, Bunk. Hey, how's it going?
听着 副局长想知道 我们追回Dozerman的佩枪了吗
Listen, Deputy wants to know, have we recovered Dozerman's service weapon?
没有 长官 那孩子说他在街上卖了
No, sir. The kid said he sold it on the street.
只说了买家的诨名
Gave only the street name of the buyer.
一个叫Peanut的 下落不明
A certain Peanut, whereabouts unknown.
他们想把枪追回来
They want that gun back.
长官?
Sir?
他们不想让局里的佩枪流落街头
They don't want to have a departmental weapon on the street.
你知道 原则问题
You know, as a principle.
听着 伟大的白人副局发话了
Look, the great white deputy has spoken.
枪不找回来就不能结案
This case is not down until that gun comes home.
没事 不用起身了
Fine, don't get up.
在这对枪宠爱有加的国度的 一个枪支泛滥的城市里
One of the most heavily armed cities in the gun-loving world...
这些无知的混球干嘛那么在意
Why should those ignorant motherfuckers care...
一把该死的半自动手枪的下落?
about one goddamn semi-auto more or less?
是什么让你在这鬼天气里把我叫出来?
What'd you bring me downtown in this shit for, man?
"湿":双关 警察不会来这儿淋雨 对他们的调查还没结束 还在"前戏"中
警察还没"湿"
Police don't get wet.
和我说说 老大
Talk to me, big man.
你该知道 我伙计 Cheese...
Thought you should know, my boy, Cheese...
他被几个警察带进去问话
he went into the box with a couple of police.
他没招吧?
He stood tall?
当然一声不吭跟他们耗
No doubt. Kept his mouth shut and waited them out.
结果是警察自己搞砸了
The way it turned out, they the ones that fucked up.
怎么回事
How come?
警察透露有Cheese的录音
Police let it slip Cheese played in on some talkies.
想指控他谋杀 号称他们都听见了
Tried to pin a hit on him. Said they heard it all over.
杀了谁
Who got hit?
一条狗
A dog.
什么"狗"?
What kind of dog?
会把你的腿错认成母狗的那种
Kind mistake your leg for pussy.
这么说他们给电话录音了?
So, they had phones tapped?
录了也扯不到我头上
Don't matter to me none if they did.
我和手下都很小心 不会在电话里嚼舌头
Me and the people I keep close, we don't talk on the phone none.
你们会在电话里说事吗 String?
You talk on the phone, String?
那我们就没事
So we good then.
我们只知道他们还咬着我们不放
What we know is they still looking hard at us.
你知道比起子弹和酒精 什么对警察更有杀伤力吗?
You wanna know what kills more police than bullets and liquor?
"无聊" 他们受不了
Boredom. They just can't handle that shit.
继续让他们无聊吧 String
You keep it boring, String.
让他们无聊死
You keep it dead fucking boring.
你来真的?
You're serious?
没错
I am.
离这最近的学校是哪所?
What's the closest school to here?
Stuart Hill小学
Stuart Hill Elementary.
离这至少八个街区
That's at least eight blocks.
- 三个七? - 三个七(赌美钞上的序列数)
- Three sevens? - Three sevens.
五个八
Five eights.
才怪 给我看看
Bullshit, let's see it.
五个八 看得让你哭吧
Five eights. Read them and weep.
你作弊
You're cheating.
- 只是抓不到你的小辫子 - 只是运气好 Tony
- I just can't catch your ass is all. - It's just luck, Tony.
运气而已
Yeah, it's just luck.
你打到我办公室找我?
You called my desk looking for me?
对 进来 请坐
Yes, I did. Come on in. Grab a chair.
不过坐下后可得小心你的钱包
But watch your wallet if you do.
长话短说吧 Tommy
Make it quick, Tommy.
新主编想给酒管局改革 做个大版面的周末特别报道
The new city editor wants a 40-inch weekender on liquor board reform.
- 他们要改革酒管局? - 对啊 用手榴弹
- They're going to reform the liquor board? - Yeah, with a hand grenade.
你有什么消息?
So what's on your mind?
我们先私下谈?
We're off the record?
今年不开警校培训班
There's going to be no academy class of police cadets this year.
市长的旨意
Mayor's orders.
凶杀案率和严重刑案正节节攀升
Homicide rate's climbing, felonies are up,
可我们的巡逻警紧缺
we got patrol vacancies out the ass.
到了年关退休潮一来 还会更棘手
Even more coming at the year-end retirements.
这是他授意的? 为什么?
And this is coming from His Honor? To what end?
为了省钱
Keep some money.
其实钱已经在预算里了 但晚六个月再招人也能省下好几百万
Money's in the budget but even a six-month delay in hiring saves a couple million.
你觉得会有什么市长签署的相关文件吗?
You think there's some paper? Something the Mayor signed?
没有 但你可以打去人事处
No, but you call the personnel office
他们会证实推迟到明年开班的消息
and they'll confirm that the class is delayed until next year.
等你确认好了 可以再到我这来采访
You get that much, you can come back to me for a couple of quotes.
要算上你吗?
You want in on this?
不必 我爱市长
No indeed. I love my Mayor.
谢谢你 议员先生
Councilman, thank you.
- 要兴风作浪? - 小打小闹而已
- Stirring up some shit? - Just a little bit.
为了我们美丽的海湾城市
For the good of our fair city by the bay.
三个二
Three twos.
房屋署要把这些瓦房拆了对吧?
Housing authority has this slated for demolition, right?
但还没钱动工
But no money to do it yet.
老大 你确定把这里瞒着有好处?
Boss, you sure it's a good idea not to tell anybody about this downtown?
无知是福啊 警督
Ignorance is bliss, Lieutenant.
没人告诉过你吗
Anyone ever tell you that?
有过一次 不过我用警棍 把那家伙狠扁了一顿
Once, but I beat the dog-piss out of the guy with a nightstick.
谁见着McNulty了
Anybody seen McNulty?
他来了再通知他
Catch him up when he posts.
新目标
New target.
Kintel Williamson 又称"王子K"
Kintel Williamson, goes by Prince K.
占据Park Circle 到Woodland大街一带街角
Has a string of corners from Park Circle to Woodland Avenue.
他还杀人
And he's dropping bodies, too.
过去四个月杀了三个
Three in the last four months.
这是我们西北区同事说的
Or so say our friends in the Northwestern District.
这么说我们不查 Proposition Joe的人了?
So we're off Proposition Joe's people?
我们把针对中层头目的逮捕 交给市刑侦部处理
We're gonna ship all the mid-level arrests downtown to C.I.D.
由缉毒科负责起诉
Let narcotics work up those prosecutions.
这之后我们就查新案子
After that, we're on to new business.
- 他看起来不成气候 - 他在杀人
- He don't look like much. - He's dropping bodies.
既然每人都肩负 降低凶杀案发生率的使命...
And with everybody pressed to bring the murder rate down...
这就是我们小组的新任务
that's the new mandate for this unit.
- Bell也血债累累呢 - 但最近没有
- Bell has bodies on him, too. - Not lately.
而Prop Joe最近也比较低调
And Prop Joe hasn't made much noise either.
他们还在贩毒 让那些小鬼打打杀杀
They're still running product. Still got kids banging out there.
现在 就因为我们让条狗毁了监听线...
And now, 'cause we blew a wire over a fucking dog...
就让他们逍遥法外
we have to let them just walk on,
继续贩毒 好像我们从一开始就是玩玩而已?
go about their shit like we were never anything to take seriously in the first place?
周末前给我写好侦查方案
I want an investigative strategy mapped up by week's end.
好在McNulty的精神犹在
Well, McNulty's here in spirit anyway.
什么
What?
就在那
Right there.
这里也行
This will work, too.
200号街区有几栋还住着人
There's a couple occupied in the 200-block
还有那边那栋
and that one over there.
但除此之外...
But otherwise...
都挺好
we're good.
好东西吧
Good shit, right?
走吧
Let's go.
- 请接Burrell局长 - 请问是哪位
- Commissioner Burrell, please. - Who's calling, please?
- 我是Carcetti议员 - 请稍候
- It's Councilman Carcetti. - Hold, please.
- 你好 - Erv 给你提个醒
- Hello. - Erv, I'm giving you a heads up.
你会接到太阳报记者的电话 打探培训班的事
You're gonna get a call from a Sun papers reporter about the academy class.
- 搞什么 你开什么玩笑 - 冷静点 Erv
- What the fuck, is this a joke? - Calm the hell down, Erv.
你只要回答"无可奉告"就好
You just "no comment" the fucker.
你说过不会提到我的名字
You tell me my name will be nowhere near this
- 结果就让个记者找上我的门? - 正是
- and then send a reporter my way? - Exactly.
然后你亲自打给市长 告诉他
Then you call the Mayor yourself and you tell him
有个记者在打探培训班延期的事
you got a reporter nosing around about the academy class getting pushed.
你说你不知道消息怎么泄露的
You tell him you have no idea how it leaked.
- 我就知道这屎盆子会扣到我头上 - 相信我 你没暴露
- I knew this shit'd come back to me. - Trust me, you're covered on this.
该死的 你怎么能让我夹在你和市长之间
God damn it, you can't hang me out there like this with the Mayor.
- 我都要嗝屁了 - 你想要那培训班吧 Erv?
- My ass is flapping in the breeze, for... - You want that class, Erv?
- 你得相信我 - 该死
- You got to trust me. - Shit!
你怎么找到我的
How you even find me?
- 碰到了Lucas - 别提他了
- Ran into Lucas. - Don't even call his name.
那小子还欠我钱呢
Nigga still owes me money.
他不过是告诉我怎么能找到你
He just told me how to find you, that's all.
他告诉了你我的近况?
He tell you how I'm doing?
嗯
Yeah...
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
你也不看看自己什么样
You ain't looking all that yourself.
你看上去不坏
You look just fine, girl.
我只想找你妹妹 就这样
Just trying to find your sister, that's all.
你配不上她了
She ain't for you no more.
我们这种人配不上她
She ain't for none of our kind.
去过郡里人的生活了
Gone out County way.
一副郡里人的穿着 那里人开的车...
Picked herself up County clothes, County car...
像郡里人挺着鼻子 瞧不起我们这些城里的黑鬼
County nose to look down on all us city niggers with.
她当上老师了
She a teacher.
- 在哪 - 别催我 混球
- Where at? - Don't be rushing me, motherfucker.
我知道你想改头换面
I know you looking to tip on out of here,
刮个胡子 喷个香水 打扮自己
get your aftershave on, get yourself correct.
她教演讲
She teach speech.
让每个人说话都像赖斯(前美国女国务卿)
Make it so every nigga sound like Condoleezza.
北边的Ida B. Wells中学
Up Ida B. Wells.
不好意思 先生 打扰了 你见过这个小女孩吗
Excuse me, sir. Excuse me, have you seen this little girl?
是我孩子 你能带上这张照片吗
This my baby. Can you just take that picture with you?
非常感谢 上帝保佑你
Thank you so much. God bless.
打扰了 你见过这个小女孩吗
Excuse me, have you seen this little girl?
- 女士 离我远点 - 她是我女儿
- Lady, you gonna have to back up. - She's my little girl.
- 求你了 她只有四岁 - 我没见过你女儿
- Please, she's only four years old. - I ain't seen your little girl.
- 快离我远点 - 求你 就看一眼
- You're gonna have to back up. - Please, just take a look at her!
- 就看看这照片... - 我没见过你女儿 你...
- Just take a look at it - I ain't seen your girl, you...
你好吗
How do?
开始吧
Let's go.
东西在哪 伙计?
Where it at, man?
在后面
Back there.
怎么样 伙计? 你想浪费我时间?
So, what up, man? You don't value my time?
黑鬼 拜托
Nigga, please.
把螺丝刀递给我 它妈的少安毋躁
Hand me that screw gun and calm the fuck down.
走 走
Go! Go!
安全
Clear!
嘿 Tosha 快走
Yo, Tosha, go!
- Dante 快走 我掩护 - 快走 Dante
- Dante, go, I got your back. - Go, Dante.
我掩护你 宝贝 我掩护你
I got you, baby. I got you.
走 走
Go! Go!
跑 Dante 快跑
Go, Dante, go!
准备好了吗
Yo, y'all ready?
我们杀出去
Let's bang out.
快跑 快跑
Go, go, go! go!
快 Kimmy 进车里去 进车里去 伙计
Come on, Kimmy, get in the car. Get in the car, man.
你的部门就像个筛子似的会泄密
Your department leaks like a fucking sieve.
也可能是市政厅的某人
It could be someone over here at the Hall.
你的收下 或是议会的谁
Someone on your staff. Someone on the Council.
无关紧要了
It doesn't matter now.
我们得尽可能地圆了这事...
We got to spin it the best way we can...
就是说你得站出来为大家扛一扛 Erv
which means we need you to step up and take this one for the team, Erv.
我?
Me?
对 告诉报纸 培训班...
Yeah. Tell the newspaper that the academy class
因某些原因被推迟
has been delayed for some reason.
生源不足 人事科出了问题
Lack of recruits, problems in your personnel division.
反正别牵连出去
Keep it in your shop.
之后 再由市长站出来...
After which, the Mayor steps in...
宣布无论如何培训班都会在一月开班
announces we'll have an academy class in January come hell or high water.
这样 这事就是过眼烟云
Do it like that, it's a one-day story.
市长先生 当初是因为预算问题
Mr. Mayor, this was a budget question.
是你授意我推迟开班
I was directed to delay that class.
对 你当时认了 现在就再担一次
Yeah, you took the hit then and you're taking the hit now.
两次我都感激你 局长大人
And I thank you for both, Commissioner.
居然有89个?
Eighty-nine?
这还只是在西区登记的
And that's just the ones with West Side addresses.
伙计 你得缩小范围
Man, you got to narrow that shit down.
找个方法调查这些"Peanuts"(花生们)
Find some way to work with all them Peanuts.
滚你妈的蛋 我看着像 George Washington Carver吗(一位美国黑人农业学家)
Motherfucker, do I look like George Washington Carver?
该死
Shit.
天杀的让我在枪满为患的地方找枪
Cocksuckers got me chasing one gun through a city full of them.
- 凶杀科 对 - 两人死亡 Pall Mall和Pimlico街
- Homicide. Yeah. - Two down, Pall Mall and Pimlico.
Pall Mall和Pimlico街 记下了
Pall Mall and Pimlico. Got it.
又有两人横尸街头
Two down in the street.
Ray Cole当班
Ray Cole's up.
Cole今天出庭
Cole is in court today
而我昨晚接了Cherry Hill的砍杀案
and I caught that cutting in Cherry Hill last night.
别看着我
Don't look at me.
我也在大海捞针 找Dozerman弄丢的枪
I'm in the haystacks, looking for Dozerman's prodigal gun.
你要让我连办两案?
You gonna make me go back-to-back as a primary?
太无情了吧 Bunk
That's some cold shit, Bunk.
木条伤人? 我觉得不算
Agg assault with a two-by-four? I don't think so.
放到第二类中
Put that with the part twos.
这个也是 持枪威胁
This one, too. Assault by pointing.
如果你不真的开枪 拿着挥来挥去也不算什么
If you don't use a handgun, you don't get credit for waving it, right?
盗窃罪 Hump写成了日间非法入侵?
Larceny here. Hump wrote this up as a daytime B and E?
去他的
Fuck this.
照章办事
Do it clean.
不要轻描淡写 不要避重就轻
Don't massage anything, don't sex anything down.
据实以告
We give them the fucking truth.
那咨情会怎么办 老大? 他们会办了你
What about COMSTAT, boss? They'll rip you.
还有5个月我就满30年了 对吧
There's five months to my 30, right?
如果他们连玩笑也开不起就算了
Fuck them if they can't take a joke.
对于这个与其他八个分局
The major no doubt has some explanation,
截然相反的每周重罪统计报表
some excuse, if you will for a weekly felony tabulation
我们的警长无疑会有所解释吧
that's going in the opposite direction from the other eight districts.
没有 长官
I have none, sir.
你对此很满意?
You are content with this?
不 副局长 我不满意
No, Deputy, I'm unhappy.
我也希望能让治安更好
I wish we were making more of an impact.
但我们的所作所为...
But doing what we're doing...
显然没有成效
it's clear that's not the case.
Colvin警长
Major Colvin,
据我所知西区的犯罪率在下降
I am under the impression crime is down in the Western.
也许你这周的重罪数统计有误
Perhaps you misfigured your felony stats this week.
不 长官 我们的统计很准确
No, sir. We were very accurate.
有时上帝就是不合作
Sometimes the gods are uncooperative.
不合作?
Uncooperative?
这是个齐心协力的结果  一个协同合作的部门
This is a cooperative effort, a cooperative department.
为什么这么说 因为在东区分局...
Why, in the Eastern District...
就在几天前 Daniels警督为我们树立了 合作精神的典范
Lieutenant Daniels exemplified this new spirit just the other day.
让我们得以破获两起谋杀 还阻止了一场毒品战争
And because of that, we got two fresh homicides in the black and a lot less bodies on the streets
避免了更多的人横尸街头
than could have been had that drug war been allowed to drag on.
为培训班延期的事 市长让我替他做挡箭牌
Mayor has me taking the hit in public for the late academy class.
- 开玩笑吧 - 我倒要问 所谓忠诚哪去了
- You're kidding me. - Where's the fucking loyalty, I ask you?
但在西区 一个经验丰富的指挥官 又给了我什么样的成绩?
But in the Western, what do I get from a veteran commander?
你在开玩笑是吧 Bunny?
You're just having a laugh, aren't you, Bunny?
真正的统计数据和投影图就在别处
You got the real stats and projections somewhere else.
有人正在门外拿着 对吧
Someone's just outside the door with them, right?
也许还是个脱衣舞娘? 那倒挺有趣的
A stripper, maybe? That would be nice.
她走进来 胴体若隐若现
She comes in, flashes a little tit
搔首弄姿 给我送上该死的统计表...
gives us a whiff of that muff and delivers my fucking stat sheets...
上面下降的数字显示 符合我们对市长的承诺
with the reduction that matches just what we promised the Mayor.
那就太完美了
That would be beautiful.
那就它妈的太漂亮了
That would be crème fucking brulée..
但我只听到一些狗屁的
But what I got instead is some half-assed
"我希望能做得更好"的陈词滥调...
"I wish we were doing better" platitude...
这也就能骗骗六岁的小女孩 只有她还觉得你尽力了吧
that's meant to fool maybe a six-year-old girl into thinking you're doing your job.
不过她现在也出去了 Colvin警长
Well, she's left the room, Major Colvin.
到外边去问那个脱衣舞娘...
She's out there right now asking the stripper...
她长大后能不能干她的活...
if she can have her job when she grows up...
因为她是肯定不想干你的工作了
because she sure as shit doesn't want yours.
知道为什么吗
You know why?
因为如果这状况再持续个20年 西区分局早就不见了
Because there isn't gonna be a goddamn Western District in 20 years if this shit keeps up.
我不管你干这行多少年
I don't care how many years you have on this job.
如果重案发生率不降下来
If the felony rate doesn't fall,
那就先把你降了
you most certainly will.
上帝要玩你 你就想法子干了他
The gods are fucking you, you find a way to fuck them back.
这是Baltimore 各位 上帝可救不了你们
It's Baltimore, gentlemen. The gods will not save you.
我不跟谁一队 我不玩...
I ain't on nobody's team. I'm not playing that...
拜托 我们是一队的
Come on. We're on the same team.
给我
Give me that.
她看着像毒贩吗
She look like a player?
看热闹的?
Bystander?
来吧 上
Come on, let's go.
如果是的话 她可是尽收眼底了
Right in the middle of it all if she was.
这儿
Over here.
趴下  他们来了
Get down, they're coming out.
嘿 轮到我做Omar了
Yo, my turn to be Omar.
不 给我 给我
No. Give it to me, gimme.
听着 我告诉你们 我当时在场
Look, I'm telling you, I was there.
那白人在909俱乐部门廊上...
White folks was on the stoop by the 909 Club...
Apex就在他身后...
and Apex just standing over his ass...
射出无数个洞来
pumping more holes in the boy than a motherfucker need.
干 我没吹牛  等那把该死的9毫米手枪不响了...
Shit, I ain't lying. Soon as that motherfucking nine stopped talking...
那白人抬头看着Apex说 "贱人 你就这点水平?"
White folks look up at Apex, say, "Bitch, that the best you got?"
伙计 我的意思是一个人有那么多血能流
Man, I'm just saying a boy got that much white blood,
一定是个硬汉
he got to be a punk.
你找我 老大?
You want me, boss?
你的数少了 Fruit
Your numbers way down, Fruit.
少了不少
Way down.
是Barksdale的手下
Man, it's Barksdale's people.
他们把从Fremont来的瘾君子都招揽了
They clipping the dope fiends coming up Fremont.
你知道 我做生意的时候 如果生意差了...
You know, when I ran a shop and my numbers dropped...
我肯定会采取些措施
I damn sure did something about it.
- 我知道了 - 让他们滚蛋
- Yeah, I hear that. - I just want them moved.
带小弟们过去 让他们锻炼锻炼
Take the young 'uns with you, give them a workout.
好的
All right.
警督 副局长今天给你戴了朵小红花 嗯?
So, Lieutenant, you got an "attaboy" from the Deputy today, huh?
却害我丢了整条监听线
It cost me my wiretap, though.
不过东区还是做得不错
Still, it's good work over in the Eastern.
阻止了一场毒品火拼
Knocking down a drug war.
他也要在Park Heights替我做同样的事
Yeah, he's gonna do the same thing for me up on Park Heights.
我要收拾收拾一个叫Kintel Williamson的家伙
I got this Kintel Williamson character who needs some fixing.
Rawls答应我 让Daniels 和他小队过来协助一个月左右
And Rawls promised me Daniels and his unit for about a month or so.
你可是声名在外啊 小子
You're getting quite the rep there, kiddo.
Stan 你东南区准备怎么办
So, Stan, what's your plan for the Southeast?
怎么给Rawls要的数字啊?
How you gonna give Rawls his numbers?
不知道啊 让机动小队出击
I don't know. Flex squads on the corners...
在Perkins Homes加班巡逻
foot patrols in the Perkins Homes, overtime out the ass.
如果这还搞不定 就只好在统计上做文章了
And if that don't work, cheat on the stats.
你怎么样
So what say you?
我? 周末还得值12小时的班 伙计
Shit, me? I'm going to 12-hour shifts on the weekend, man.
你呢 Bunny?
What about you, Bunny?
不知道
I don't know.
我考虑着干脆让毒品合法化吧
I thought I might legalize drugs.
他们袭击了那该死的小巷 我们候着他们呢
So they hit the goddamn alley. And we on them.
那个抗着大枪的死基佬?
That cocksmoking motherfucker with the big-bitch gun?
我们紧追不舍 不过...
We was running hard on his ass, but...
我想我打中他了
I think I hit him.
小子 你谁也没打中
Nigga, you ain't hit nobody.
我能打中他的
I might've hit him.
嘿 String 我们干掉了一个女的
Yo, String, we hit the one girl.
这之后 就没人中弹了 伙计
But after that, man, I ain't seen nobody catch no lead, man.
- 除了Tank - 对 Tank挂了
- Except for Tank. - Yeah, Tank gone.
另一个女的放倒了他 所以我猜我们扯平了
The other broad dropped him. So I guess we're even now.
这么说你们干掉了一个 对吧
So you get one, right?
对
Yeah.
很好 就像个40度的天气
That's good. That's like a 40-degree day.
40度没人会说什么
Ain't nobody got nothing to say about a 40-degree day.
50度 人们露出笑颜
Fifty. Bring a smile to your face.
60度 靠 黑鬼们都可以烤肉了
Sixty, shit, niggas is damn near barbecuing on that motherfucker.
降到20度 就开始抱怨
Go down to 20, niggas get their bitch on.
满嘴牢骚 但40度?
Get their blood complaining. But 40?
没人会在意40度 谁会记得40度
Nobody give a fuck about 40. Nobody remember 40,
你们给了我太多40度的天 搞什么
and y'all niggas is giving me way too many 40-degree days. What the fuck?
现在我们在那贱人的葬礼 在她的守灵那天埋伏好
Now, we gonna cover that bitch's funeral, her fucking wake.
一路都守着 直到臭婊子下葬
We're gonna be all over that motherfucker, till the bitch hit the ground.
如果那死基佬跑来祭奠...
And if the faggot roll up to pay his respects...
就抓住那混球 嘿 你他妈跟谁说话呢?
we're gonna be on that motherfucker. Who the fuck you talking to, man?
是Donette...String 她一直打过来
It's Donette, String. She been calling.
不 把电话挂了
No, put the phone down.
你们都明白了吗
Are you all feeling me on this?
- 明白 - 明白
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
他出现 我们就拿下他 就像...
He show up, we on him like a motherfucking...
就像40度的天
Like a 40-degree day.
总的来说 重罪案件减少了
So overall, felonies are down.
但凶案还是居高不下 下一步怎么办
But murders are still up. What's our next move?
允许我调高加班费和奖励幅度
Let me bump overtime
给到凶杀组和行动队
and court pay for homicide and district ops.
破案"go into the black"之前 要先撒钱"go into the green"
重赏之下必有勇夫
Cases go into the green before they go into the black.
可以
Done.
当然 如果法院能给点力 会大有帮助
And of course, if we could get some help at the courthouse, it would go a long way.
嘿 就算你想找活路
Hey, if you're going to try and dig your way out of this...
也别拿我当挖路的铲子
don't make me your shovel.
我的部门提交的案子都无疾而终
My department is bringing you casework that goes nowhere.
那些案子证据薄弱
The cases are thin.
很多连新手法官的预审都通不过
Most wouldn't make it past a prelim in the court of a freshman judge.
也许如果你的员工能不那么在乎...
Well, maybe if your personnel weren't so goddamn concerned...
他们该死的定罪率 他们也许就能碰上一两起"谜案"(而不是只挑简单的案子审理)
for their goddamn conviction rate, they'd chance a whodunit or two.
看在上帝的份上...
For Christ's sake...
老天 至少也该假装你们是同一阵线的吧
Jesus, at least pretend you're on the same side.
Stephen 你我明年这个时候都得竞选
Stephen, you and I are both going to be counting votes this time next year.
做点事情帮帮大家吧
Do something to help our sorry asses.
而Erv 如果你不只是想 代理完Walker的任期...
And Erv, if you want to do more than just finish out Walker's term...
就给点成绩 别光推卸责任
show me something more than just a pass of the buck.
我想我们中没谁想找份真正的工作干吧
I don't think any of us wants to have to get a real job.
- 再见 市长先生 - 好了
- Mr. Mayor. - All right.
- 下周在这跟你俩接着谈 - 谢谢 长官
- I'll see you both in here on this next week. - Thank you, sir.
都跟孩子似地
They're like children.
Demper一直是朽木不可雕
Demper's always been a hack.
但他好歹是选出来的 所以我们只能忍了
But he's an elected hack, so we're stuck with him.
Burrell则不然
But Burrell, though.
犯罪率是你的软肋 Clarence
You're vulnerable on crime, Clarence.
你得踢开某些废物
You need to set some deadwood adrift.
- Burrell有朋友 - 那些牧师?
- Burrell's got friends. - The ministers?
他也许跟他们称兄道弟 可你也一样
Well, he might be their man, but so are you.
炒掉Burrell 加入些新鲜血液...
You fire Burrell, you get some new blood in here...
犯罪率自然就下降了 懂吗
the crime rate drops, huh?
牧师们不会有意见的
The ministers will live with it.
看来你对废物毫不留情
So you're tough on deadwood, huh?
听说你对新11区也是?
In the new 11th district, too, I hear.
市长先生 Eunetta该走了
Mr. Mayor, it's time for Eunetta to go.
她已经风光过 外面有更适合的议员人选
She's had her time. There are better people out there for the Council.
她是我们一条船上的 Odell
She's on the team, Odell.
我的警察局长也是
Just like my police commissioner.
我重忠诚 你不也是吗
I value loyalty. Don't you?
小Bunk 我的Bunk哪去了
Bunky Bunk, where's my Bunk?
Cole当班 不是你
Cole was up, not you.
你要查Dozerman的枪 记得吗
You're on Dozerman's gun, remember?
Cole在法院 告我去啊
Cole was at the courthouse. Sue me.
Rawls和Foerster已经撑紧了我的菊花
Rawls and Foerster have crawled up into my backside...
在你找到Dozerman的枪前 他们是不会放过那儿了
and they're gonna stay there until you find Dozerman's gun.
我实在是太想让我的大屁股放松放松了
Now, I would like it very much if I could unclench my ample ass cheeks...
如果你愿意 请帮我解脱
if you don't mind, and rid myself of that discomfort.
Jay 有个案子至关重要 不得不办
Jay, I just caught one that pushed its way all the way to the top of my stack.
一个被害人 Jay
A victim, Jay.
- 真正的受害人 - 那就说说
- On the real side. - Do tell.
在一起双尸案中的二号
Second body in a double.
20来岁的姑娘 卷入一场枪战 一枪正中脑门
Girl in her 20s, caught in the middle of a firefight. Takes one in the dome.
但她死在一个无关紧要的地方
But she's still dead in a zip code that does not fucking matter.
而你还欠着我一把 警局配发的九毫米手枪
And you still owe me a departmental-issue nine.
找回那把该死的枪 Bunk
Find the fucking gun, Bunk.
纸上是绰号"Peanut"的人的名单
我靠
Fuck me.
Kintel Williamson? 哪个杂种?
Kintel Williamson, who the fuck?
- 他在Park Heights有街角 - 老天 谁没有
- He has corners in Park Heights. - But Jesus, who doesn't?
我们打了你一天电话 Jimmy 好奇你去哪儿了
So all day we're calling you, Jimmy, wondering where you're at.
Kima 也许你能告诉我们
Kima, maybe you can enlighten us.
别看着我
Don't look at me.
这哥们也没告诉我这些天他上哪去了
My running buddy don't even tell me where he's off to these days.
- 我在图书馆 - 放屁
- I was at the library. - Bullshit.
我在州立监狱的图书馆
I was at the library at M.C.I. Jessup.
D'Angelo Barksdale不是自杀
D'Angelo Barksdale was not a suicide.
验尸官告诉你的?
The M.E. tell you that?
不需要 实物证据根本不匹配(勒绳太长 勒不死自己)
He didn't need to. The physical evidence didn't match up.
听着 我跟你一样 都不想放弃Stringer和Prop Joe
Look, I don't like coming up off of Stringer or Prop Joe any more than you do.
但 McNulty 这点证据可不够
But, McNulty, this shit is kind of weak.
Cedric压力很大 大家都指望借他的小组来降低凶案率
Cedric is under a lot of pressure to use this unit to get the murder rate down.
所以眼下 查Stringer Bell还是缉毒科的事
So for now, Stringer Bell's jacket belongs in narcotics.
是他让你"下了船" Jimmy(调离了水警队)
Man took you off a boat, Jimmy.
他想让"他的"小组转移目标
He want to peel his unit off, his unit, Jimmy...
去查他想查的目标 宝贝 那就得听他的
and go after the target of his choice, baby, it's his call.
Lester 我还以为你只想查最棒的案子呢
Lester, I thought you were all about the best case possible.
有的话 我就上
When it's there, I am.
你们听我说
Yo, I need y'all to hear this, man.
这是我的错
It was my fault.
听见了吗
You hear me?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry, yo.
这对我没有用
That don't do nothing for me.
怎么会这样...
How come...
她们和你交往时 知道你是警察...
they know you're police when they hook up with you...
搬进来同居时 知道你是警察...
and they know you're police when they move in...
决定要成家时 知道你是警察...
and they know you're police when they decide to start a family with you...
一切都很好 直到有一天全变了
and all that shit is just fine until one day it ain't.
她开始说 "你该找份平常的工作..."
One day it's, "You should have a regular job...
"要在5点到家"
"you need to be home at 5:00."
"要多打电话"
"You need to call more."
正要说呢
I'm saying.
"别再跟女服务生乱搞"
"You need to stop fucking waitresses."
我明天想到西区这边瞅瞅
I wanna come down here tomorrow to Western.
看看高楼倒了后成什么样了
See what's what since those Towers came down.
我们明天得开始查Kintel了
We're supposed to start on Kintel tomorrow.
谁管那个傻逼 他再等两天也无所谓
Fuck that chump. He can wait a day or two.
好吧 管他呢
Yeah, okay. What the fuck.
当初你在西区开车巡逻时 这算你的窝吗?
When you were humping a radio car in the Western, was this your hole?
对
Yeah.
这儿还有Winchester那边桥底下
Here and down on Winchester, under the bridge.
我打赌你一定很多晚上不回家陪老婆
Bet there were a lot of nights you didn't go home to the missus.
别告诉我 我跟你是同类
Don't tell me I'm the same kind of asshole.
来啵一个 女朋友
Pucker up, girlfriend.
老天 我要变成McNulty了
Jesus! I'm turning into McNulty.
嘿 我准备好出发了
Hey. I'm getting ready to go now.
不 奶奶 你知道我不能要
No, Mee-maw, you know I can't.
这年头 宝贝 你得表现表现
Times like these, honey, you have to shine.
脸蛋 衣服 还有口袋
In your face, in your clothes, and in your pocket.
现在 去吧
Now, go on.
那你别饿了自己 好吗
Make sure you get something to eat, hear?
去吧
Go on, now.
- 认识他们吗? - 不认识
- You know them? - Not a clue.
对角那边还挺眼熟的
The crew on that corner looks familiar.
几张老面孔
A couple old faces.
不是很多
Not many.
离开一年 整个世界都变了
You go away for a year and the whole world changes up.
不过很平静
Quiet, though.
Barksdale丢了高楼 居然没伤一兵一卒 就爬到别人的地盘上?
Barksdale loses the Towers and he's able to stretch out without bodies falling?
我真想知道西区的伙计们 近来的所见所闻
I wonder what the Western guys have been seeing lately.
喂 嘿 Jay
Yeah. Hey, Jay.
- 你有空吗 - 有
- You have a minute? - Yeah.
- 发生什么事了 几时 - 他就是一倒不起了
- What the fuck happened? when? - He just collapsed.
什么时候?
when?
他怎么样了
How is he?
靠
Shit.
- 你会通知我 对吧 - 嗯
- You're gonna let me know, right? - Yeah.
好的 嗯 谢谢
Okay, yeah. Thanks.
- 认识Ray Cole吗 - 凶杀科的 对吧
- You know Ray Cole? - Homicide, right?
今早他倒在了市中心健身房里
Collapsed in the gym at the Central District this morning.
在台该死的蹬步机上
On a fucking Stairmaster.
他怎么样了
Well, how is he?
蹬步机?!
A Stairmaster.
嘿 Poot 你看
Hey, Poot, check it out.
- 他们哪去了 - 不知道
- Where they at? - I don't know.
该死 上 上 小心 伙计
Shit! Go! Go! Look out, man!
停下 够了 混球们
Break it, break, motherfuckers.
- 他说停下 好了 - 我正揍得起劲呢
- Man said break. Come on. - I was working that bitch.
是啊 小子 你够狠
Yeah, shorty, you hard.
走 离开这
Go. We out of here.
"局长承认预算中 有用于培训班的资金..."
"The Commissioner acknowledged that money had been budgeted for the academy class...
"但表示在将计划排上日程前 警局正等待一笔..."
"but said the department was awaiting approval of a federal training and education grant
"联邦培训和教育补助金的审批"
"before scheduling the program."
Burrell真能放屁 不是吗
Burrell can talk some shit, can't he?
城里人大驾光临
Downtown in the house.
- 嘿 Kima宝贝 - 嘿 Ellis
Hey, Kima baby. Hey, Ellis.
Herc
Herc.
我们何以有此荣幸
So, what do we owe the pleasure?
刚在你们辖区转了转 看到了高楼倒掉后的变化
Cruising your district, seeing what's up since the Towers fell.
我们看见Barksdale的人占了几个街角 但似乎没人去找他们生事
We see Barksdale crews on a few corners, but no one seems to be beefing with them.
这么和睦是怎么回事
What's up with all this brotherhood?
多亏我们盯得紧啊 他们知道我们不是朋友...
We keep the lid on tight. You know, they know we're not their friends...
他们清楚如果不乖乖的 我们会给他们什么颜色看
and they damn well know that we'll take it to them if they don't behave.
你们的线人怎么说
What do your C.I.'s tell you?
去他的线人 我们才不需要臭线人
Fuck C.I.'s. We don't need no stinking C.I.'s.
我们对那帮人一抓 二打 三关
We tune 'em up, we beat 'em down, we lock 'em up.
西区就这么办事
It's the Western District way.
警司 你被指名参加一个主管会议
Sergeant, you're wanted in roll call for a supervisor's meeting.
该走了
Gotta go.
记得我怎么跟你说的吗 线人厉害了 警察才能变得厉害
Remember what I told you? Police is only as good as his informants.
但我们已经不是在城里了 Kima 我们在战壕里
Yeah, well, we ain't downtown no more, Kima. We're in the trenches here.
想要情报 找你自己的线人去 自己去打听吧
You want information, you go get your own C. I. And you shoot the shit.
你迟到了 警司
You're late, Sergeant.
有俩城里的警探来我的地盘
I had a couple of downtown detectives in my shop.
他们很迷茫请求协助 长官
They were confused and required assistance, sir.
待会再找你
Well, I'll catch you up.
我们区的新策略
The new strategic plan for the district
要将所有街头的非法交易 赶进这三个区域
is to move all street-level trafficking to these three areas.
我们要推一把
We want to push it.
推一把 老大?
Push it, boss?
如果不吃软的 就给他们尝硬的
If they don't go easy, then they go hard.
但我们要让这些傻瓜知道...
But we let these knuckleheads know...
如果他们转移到这些地方 远离居民区...
that if they move to these areas, away from the residential streets...
远离商业区 学校...
away from commercial areas, away from schools...
如果他们把货带到这来卖...
if they take that shit down the road...
我们就不干涉他们生意
they can go about their business without any interference from us.
在可预见的将来 这些地区将是西区的不干涉区域
It's going to be hands-off in the Western District for the foreseeable future.
胡说八道
Bullshit, man.
- 没门 - 等等
- No fucking way. - Wait.
你是说让我们给他们"免费入场券"?
You're saying you want us to give them a free pass?
- 我们还怎么面对他们? - 就是
- How're we going to look them in the eye? - Yeah.
他们会藐视我们 让他们的兔崽子藐视我们
They'll shit all over us, tell their kids to shit all over us.
嘿 警长还没说完呢
Hey, the Major wasn't finished.
你们得把眼光放长远些
You got to take the long view here.
一旦...
Once...
一旦他们适应了 盘踞在一起...
Once they're all comfortable, once they are all rounded up...
等他们在那待了一段时间 习惯到能翘着双脚...
once they've been down there a bit and they're used to putting their feet up...
玩他们的电视遥控器
and playing with the remote,
我们就行动了
then we move.
我们杀回去 做我们的工作
Then we go back and we do police work.
你们该这么看
Look at it this way, gentlemen.
你是愿意在茫茫大海里开鱼枪呢...
Would you rather shoot at fish in the ocean...
还是愿意把它们放养在几个桶里...
or would you rather gather them up in a few small barrels...
再一条条射上来?
and start emptying your clips then?
更何况 你们还是可以把那些死守的家伙
Not to mention, you still get to kick the shit out of all the mopes...
揍个眼冒金星
that don't move off our corners.
所以也不赖
So it ain't all bad.
慢点 姑娘
Slow up, girl.
拜托
Come on, now.
这是你的座驾?
So this your ride?
- 不错 - 我想你有辆雷克萨斯了吧
- It's nice. - I suppose you got a Lex.
不 我只有公交车票
No, girl. Got a bus pass.
- 你已经不混了? - 嗯
- You out the game, then? - yeah.
现在做起了绿化 不过还是再找方向
Doing a little landscaping right now but trying to figure things out.
你儿子叫什么名字
So what's your boy's name?
Allen
Allen.
- 取自艾弗森?(阿伦.艾弗森 篮球明星) - 取自他爸
- After lverson? - After his daddy.
干嘛
What?
我在想象你割草坪的样子
I'm trying to picture you mowing a lawn.
是啊 我不适合穿这身
Yeah, I don't be wearing this suit.
- 不过穿着挺好的 - 你也是
- You look good in it, still. - You look good, too.
你知道
You know,
公园游憩管理局(一个有综合职能的城建部门)提前买断了很多人的工龄
they bought a lot a folks out with early retirement in Parks and Rec.
我也许可以替你牵牵线
I could maybe hook you up with someone to talk to.
我去的教堂里有个人就是招这类的
A man at my church is helping the city fill a lot of those jobs.
那就... 谢了
That would be... thank you.
写上你电话
Write your number there.
他会联系你
He'll call you.
我该走了
I gotta go.
很高兴见到你
It was good seeing you.
Grace
Grace.
看着你...
Looking at you...
怎么
What?
心痛
Hurts.
那你本就不该看
You shouldn't look then.
教区厨房 免费午餐时间 周二 周四 周五 午间至三点
食物会让你忘了它
A food blast will take your mind off it.
我宁可想着它 Bubs
I'd rather my mind on it, Bubs.
我发誓 我厌烦了这一切 伙计
I swear, I'm sick of all of this, man.
真想知道何时能老
Wondering when I got so old.
多给点干酪通心粉吧
Some more mac and cheese, huh?
嘿 Bubs
Hey, Bubs.
- Kima - 嘿 Bub
- Kima. - Hey, Bub.
McNutty 伙计 我最要好的朋友
McNutty, man. My mainest man.
- 想干点活吗 - 时刻准备着
- You ready to put some work in? - Born ready.
- 告密? 去他的 Bubs - 不 伙计
- Snitching? Fuck that, Bubs. - Hey, no, man.
总好过搬个500磅的散热器吧
Better than lifting 500-pound radiators.
他们要用我 Johnny 这钱好赚
I'm up for these two, Johnny. That's easy money, man.
走 我们去吃汉堡
Come on, let's grab a burger.
介意我先闪吗 Cole的事让我不好受
You mind if I bang out of here early? I ain't right with this Cole thing.
今晚会在Kavanagh家吧守灵 你要来吗
There's gonna be a detectives' wake at Kavanagh's tonight. You gonna come?
我和他谈不上认识 你们打算让他躺在吧台上?
I barely knew the guy. You all laying him out at the bar, huh?
老传统 明晚再把他送去殡仪馆让家人陪
Tradition. Tomorrow night, he goes to the funeral home for family.
今晚 Ray要与大家一醉方休
Tonight, Ray drinks with the boys.
走了 Bubs 我们时间不多
Come on, Bubs. We ain't got all day.
欢迎参加第25届牛肉与牡蛎烧烤年会  东部联盟民主党俱乐部
他想参加改选...
He's up for re-election...
Goo-goo:想优化政府的政治改革派
但他的改组提案从来没被通过
and he's never had a single one of his goo-goo bills pass the committee.
所以他这次想出了全日制幼儿园
So, he's got one for all-day kindergarten.
我是说谁会对多几个幼儿园有意见?
I mean who's gonna argue with more kindergarten?
我的意思是 这家伙的提案
I mean, this guy has got a bill...
就相当于法律上认同可以亲吻孩子
which is the legislative equivalent of kissing a baby.
然后他去见主席 呈上议案并说...
So, right, he goes to his chairman, pleads his case and says...
"你知道 这个再不通过 我就完了..."
"You know, this don't go through, I'm torched...
"就得回到五金商店调漆去"
"and I'm going to be back in that hardware store, mixing paint."
主席很同情他 就同意了 将议案提上议程
So, the chairman takes pity and agrees. He gets the bill to the floor.
但议长讨厌这项议案
But the house speaker, he hates this bill.
所以它生不逢时
So, it gets loved to death, you know.
还有另一项耗资1亿5千万的 补助金 接济品的修正案
Slap on an amendment for another $150 million in costs subsidies, handouts
而那项议案岌岌可危
and the bill goes down in flames.
122对10  那个代表... 他都快闻到油漆罐的味道了
122 to 10. The delegate, he can smell those paint cans.
主席说"抱歉了 哥们"
And the chairman says, "Hey, sorry, brother.
"我为这议案已经拼劲全力了"
"I fought like a tiger for that bill."
- 这算什么朋友... - 干这行你想找朋友?
- With friends like that... - You want friends? In this racket?
养条狗吧
Get a dog.
- 什么 - 听着 我们真的很忙
- What? - Look, we're real busy.
- 我要跟他谈 - 我会传话给他
- I need to talk to him. - I gave him the message.
- 听着 告诉他我是Donette - 你确定他认识你?
- Look, just tell him it's Donette. - You're sure he knows you?
对 他知道我他妈是谁
Yeah, he know who the fuck I am.
- 嘿 String 她说... - 现在不行
- Yo, String, she said... - Not now.
听着 他说现在不行 我要挂了
Look, he say not now. I got to go.
Marlo? 他是个麻烦 String
Marlo? It's a problem, String.
酸橙苏打水
Club soda and lime.
你这样可达不到目的
You'll never get there that way.
什么目的
Get where?
失陪
Excuse me.
我怎么知道市长会让你当替罪羊
How the hell was I to know the Mayor was gonna put the screws to you?
看过报纸了? 我真是灰头土脸
You read the paper? I look like shit.
嘿 至少你的培训班有了
Hey, you got your class.
还很可能让Royce市长看到了 你的赤胆忠心 不是吗?
And probably scored points with Royce out of sheer loyalty, right?
我们...是警察
We are police.
所以我们之间不说谎
So no lies between us.
他不是最好的警察
He wasn't the greatest detective
但也不是最差的
and he wasn't the worst.
他破过一些案子  也搞砸过一些
He put down some good cases and he dogged a few bad ones.
但这混球也风光过 对 没错
But the motherfucker had his moments. Yes, he fucking did.
你们记得Mississippi引渡案吗
You remember the Mississippi extradition?
- Arson谋杀案? - 对
- The arson murders? - Right.
他查了个水落石出
He brought that case home.
还有Hudson街三尸案...
And the triple at the after-hours over on Hudson Street...
那是Ray Cole的最佳杰作
that was Ray Cole at his best.
还有93年Fayette街的毒品大战
And Fayette Street in '93, the drug wars.
他端了不少街角 平息了一切
He took a lot of hot corners and cooled them.
是的 没错
Yes, indeed.
他毁誉参半
He won as much as he lost.
跟我们一样
Much as any of us.
看在上帝的份上 放那该死的歌吧
For Christ's sake, Hugh, play the fucking song, already.
他惹恼过的老婆是一个还是三个?
Did he piss off a wife or three?
毫无疑问
No fucking doubt.
我想最后一个总算习惯了他吧 谢天谢地
I think the last one actually kind of got used to him, thank God.
他有没有满嘴胡言过
Did he say the wrong shit now and then?
他有没有耍过人 逃过税...
Did he bust balls and cheat on his taxes...
忘了给老妈打电话 上错女人
and forget to call his mother and fuck the wrong broad...
借着一些狗屁理由?
for the wrong fucking reason every now and then?
老天 谁他妈没有过呢!
Who fucking doesn't? Christ!
他是否和其他Baltimore警察局
Was he as full of shit as every other sad-sack motherfucker
带着徽章的草包一样废呢
wearing a badge of Baltimore City Police?
他妈的就是!
Abso-fucking-lutely.
他跟我们一样废 毫无疑问
His shit was as weak as ours, no question.
但Ray Cole跟我们一块...
But Ray Cole stood with us...
和所有的人...
all of us...
在Baltimore...
in Baltimore...
美国国父们提出并一直致力的民主政治改革
工作着 分享着"美国实验"里的一个阴暗角落
working, sharing a dark corner of the American experiment.
他接受召唤
He was called.
他服务于民
He served.
他是条好汉
He is counted.
- 老Cole王 - 老Cole王
- Old King Cole. - Old King Cole!
《The Body of an American》 演唱:The Pogues
* The cadillac stood by the house *
* And the yanks they were within *
* The tinker boys, they hissed advice *
* "Hot-wire her with a pin" *
* Then we turned and shook as we had a look *
* In the room where the dead men lay *
* So big jim dwyer made his last trip *
* To the shore where his father's laid *
* But 15 minutes later *
* We had our first taste of whiskey *
* There was uncles giving lectures *
* On ancient irish history *
* The men all started telling jokes *
* And the women they got frisky *
* At 5:00 in the evening, every bastard there was piskey *
* Fare thee well going away *
* There's nothing left to say *
* Farewell to new york city, boys *
* To boston and p.A. *
* He took them out with a well-aimed clout *
* He was often heard to say *
* "I'm a free-born man of the U.S.A.!" *
对不起 但我要送小家伙们回家了
I'm sorry, but I gotta get these guys home.
但总的来说 他们表现挺好
But all things considered, I think they did pretty well.
他们很棒 你也很棒 真的 Jen
They were great. And you were great, really, Jen.
再说 我想他们拍到够多的家庭照了
Besides, I think they got all the family shots they need.
- 你还得再待会 是吧? - 嗯哼
- So, you'll be a while, though, huh? - un-hum.
再去招呼一下大家 你知道
Got to work the crowd, you know.
- 让他们觉得我值得他们信任 - 你值得...
- Make them think I'm worthy of their faith. - You are...
- 谢谢 - 大部分时间是吧
- Well, thank you. - Most of the time.
小坏蛋
Bitch.
能早走就别太晚了 好吗
Not too late if you can help it, okay?
Jimmy
Jimmy.
Jimmy Jimmy Jimmy
Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy.
什么鬼世界
Shit is fucked.
他妈的每天醒来都一个样
You fucking wake up like any other day.
吃饭
You fucking eat
想着账单和干洗衣服什么的...
and think about bills and dry-cleaning and shit...
想着假期 退休计划 然后呢
and fucking vacation and your fucking retirement plan and what?
就像那样走了
Like that.
就像那样
他再回头看看这儿
He checked out of here...
你还欠他一宗Omar的案子未结呢
with you still owing him a clearance on that Omar thing.
知道 知道 我他妈知道
I know, I know. I fucking know.
就像那样
Like that.
倒在TMD蹬步机上
On a fucking Stairmaster.
倒在他妈的蹬步机上
起来好好死 贱B们
Wake up and die right, you cunts.
Tosha Mitchell女士
怎么样了 伙计?
What's going on, man?
那车真不错 改天我也要给自己搞一辆
That whip is pretty. I gotta get me one of them joints one day.
靠 没错
Shit, yeah.